// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Where is our resort located?",
    answer: "Galle",
    options: [
      "Galle",
      "Colombo",
      "Jaffna",
      "Kandy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When was our resort build?",
    answer: "1995",
    options: [
      "1995",
      "1999",
      "2000",
      "2022"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The most rooms sold for hotels are done through?",
    answer: "Travel agents",
    options: [
      "Travel agents",
      "A consolidator",
      "The Internetgns",
      "A tour package"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the most expensive food on resort?",
    answer: "Wagyu beef pie",
    options: [
      "Kottu",
      "Fried Rice",
      "Pizza",
      "Wagyu beef pie"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many events has resort released so far?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the first public room on the resort is?",
    answer: "Outside Spaces",
    options: [
      "Theatre Domes",
      "Welcome Room",
      "Outside Spaces",
      "Welcome Lounge"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many rooms does resort have?",
    answer: "20",
    options: [
      "2",
      "7",
      "10",
      "20"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How much of a deposit is generally required when making a deposit for a guest room at a hotel?",
    answer: "Full payment",
    options: [
      "One days rent",
      "At least one dollar",
      "Full payment",
      "100 US Dollars"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Name one factor that could affect the price of a hotel room?",
    answer: "The size of the hotel",
    options: [
      "The size of the hotel",
      "The hotel's prime market",
      "The hotel lobby furnishings",
      "The ours of operation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What do you think of resort?",
    answer: "Very Good",
    options: [
      "Very Good",
      "Good",
      "Bad",
      "Very Bad"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];